<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cilium on UltTransformer</title>
    <link>https://ulttransformer.com/tags/cilium/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cilium on UltTransformer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ulttransformer.com/tags/cilium/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GKE Deep Dive by A Cloud Guru</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/gke-deep-dive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/gke-deep-dive/</guid>
      <description>After watching the GKE Deep Dive course provided by ACloudGuru/Pluralsight, I felt a little disappointed. While I never want to discourage people from publishing content as it helps us all learn, I felt the course should be (re)named to GKE Getting Started.
The course has value, showing general GKE concepts and providing how-to videos, so if you are a GCP novice or a K8s novice, then this course is definitely worth checking out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Networking with Kubernetes on AWS by A Cloud Guru</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/advanced-networking-with-kubernetes-on-aws-by-a-cloud-guru/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/advanced-networking-with-kubernetes-on-aws-by-a-cloud-guru/</guid>
      <description>The K8s Advanced Networking course by A Cloud Guru is fantastic, as one would expect from one of the leading Cloud education tools. It focuses on AWS EKS and has clear and concise explanations, with labs where appropriate to get some hands-on experience.
While I thoroughly enjoyed the course and the labs, I would have liked a bit more depth and discussion around the design decisions. The concepts are always explained from a high-level, occasionally low level, but to truly understand EKS Networking, further exploration is required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K8s &amp; Cilium Study Guide</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/k8s-cilium-study-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/k8s-cilium-study-guide/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes or K8s is not a new topic in the world of technology, but I feel it&amp;rsquo;s one that is discussed regularly without a deep level of understanding. As ever, I&amp;rsquo;m curious to learn how it works, where it can, and more importantly, should be applied, and the architectural decisions that go along with it.
For those reasons, I decided to start learning K8s, and more specifically K8s Networking because of my background as a Network Architect.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
