<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VCDX on UltTransformer</title>
    <link>https://ulttransformer.com/tags/vcdx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in VCDX on UltTransformer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ulttransformer.com/tags/vcdx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NSX CSM (Cloud Service Manager)</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/nsx/nsx-csm-cloud-service-manager-ca-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/nsx/nsx-csm-cloud-service-manager-ca-certificate/</guid>
      <description>I recently worked on a customer project where they replaced the NSX Manager certificate with a company-signed certificate using their own CA. This caused an issue when pairing the CSM with the NSX Manager, i.e. certificate error.
This short blog post will run through the steps ran through to allow the CSM to peer with the NSX Manager. I understand this post won’t receive a lot of traffic, my hope is it helps someone in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCDX-NV</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-289/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-289/</guid>
      <description>On Monday 14th of September 2020, I remotely sat the VCDX defence and the following Tuesday, I received the fantastic news that I passed. I am officially VCDX number 289!
For those of you that are new to vMusketeers and my VCDX blogs, here are a link to the previous 3 blogs and a vBrownBag video:
The design document The design defence The scenario defence VCDX motivation (vBrownBag) The experienceI spent a lot of time talking to and working with existing VCDX’s and VCDX applicants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCDX-NV</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-defence-scenario/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-defence-scenario/</guid>
      <description>Due to the virus outbreak, my VCDX defence has been postponed until the next window, which is June. The VCDX board decided, understandably, to keep their panellists and applicants as safe as possible. That said, I thought I’d continue the blogging trend and discuss another area of preparation.
Still excited as 3 months will fly by! I’ve discussed the document and design defence. Now let’s look at the defence scenario.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCDX-NV</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-design-defence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-design-defence/</guid>
      <description>I am waiting to hear back on my defence invite, but am preparing like I’ve been invited. Solid advice any VCDX will give you. The design defence is an invitation to Palo Alto, Staines or Sydney to defend your design and run through a scenario. In today’s blog, I am going to talk about my experience when preparing for the design defence.
The design defence is you defending your submitted design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCDX-NV</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-document-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-document-submission/</guid>
      <description>To start my blogging career, I thought I would talk about my VCDX-NV journey.
I’m currently in the waiting stage after submitting my documents. Waiting for a VCDX panel to determine if my documentation warrants an invite to defend.
Whilst waiting, I thought I’d take this time to share some advice that I found useful on my journey.
Firstly, read and understand the blueprint this can’t be stressed enough. During your journey; you will find all VCDXs repeat this phrase to you, and it’s true.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
