<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on UltTransformer</title>
    <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on UltTransformer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ulttransformer.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GKE Deep Dive by A Cloud Guru</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/gke-deep-dive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/gke-deep-dive/</guid>
      <description>After watching the GKE Deep Dive course provided by ACloudGuru/Pluralsight, I felt a little disappointed. While I never want to discourage people from publishing content as it helps us all learn, I felt the course should be (re)named to GKE Getting Started.
The course has value, showing general GKE concepts and providing how-to videos, so if you are a GCP novice or a K8s novice, then this course is definitely worth checking out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Networking with Kubernetes on AWS by A Cloud Guru</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/advanced-networking-with-kubernetes-on-aws-by-a-cloud-guru/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/advanced-networking-with-kubernetes-on-aws-by-a-cloud-guru/</guid>
      <description>The K8s Advanced Networking course by A Cloud Guru is fantastic, as one would expect from one of the leading Cloud education tools. It focuses on AWS EKS and has clear and concise explanations, with labs where appropriate to get some hands-on experience.
While I thoroughly enjoyed the course and the labs, I would have liked a bit more depth and discussion around the design decisions. The concepts are always explained from a high-level, occasionally low level, but to truly understand EKS Networking, further exploration is required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K8s &amp; Cilium Study Guide</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/k8s-cilium-study-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/cilium/k8s-cilium-study-guide/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes or K8s is not a new topic in the world of technology, but I feel it&amp;rsquo;s one that is discussed regularly without a deep level of understanding. As ever, I&amp;rsquo;m curious to learn how it works, where it can, and more importantly, should be applied, and the architectural decisions that go along with it.
For those reasons, I decided to start learning K8s, and more specifically K8s Networking because of my background as a Network Architect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris&#39; Corner - May 2023</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/chris-corner-may-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/chris-corner-may-2023/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is a copy of my env0 post.
Introductionenv0 has released 3 key features this month, directly helping new and existing customers. One of our features has already been covered in a separate blog, the Private provider registry.
Remote state access control - Share state between projects within env0. Private provider registry - Use both public and private providers. Private plugins - Integrate your own privately hosted plugin. Project-level remote backend enforcement - Force env0 remote state on all deployments within a Project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris&#39; Corner - April 2023</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/chris-corner-april-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/chris-corner-april-2023/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is a copy of my env0 post.
IntroductionIn the second iteration of Chris’ Corner, we will review the features released in the month of March. There were only 2 released last month, but no need to panic, they are both great features.
Sub Projects - Create project granularity within env0, allowing users to create a hierarchical structure. PR Comments With Role-Based Access - Map your VCS provider user to your env0&amp;rsquo;s custom roles, and enforce their permissions while using the PR comment flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provider Registry</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/provider-registry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/provider-registry/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is a copy of my env0 post.
What is it and why do we need it?Providers are used by Terraform as a set of instructions on how to interact with an endpoint. Put simply, if you want to automate the build of your env0 structure, you can use Terraform in conjunction with the env0 Provider. Terraform is the engine, the Provider handles the directions.
The eco-system is filled with open source Providers that are hosted on Hashicorp public Provider Registry, to mention a few:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris&#39; Corner - March 2023</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/chris-corner-march-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/chris-corner-march-2023/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is a copy of my env0 post.
IntroductionThe development within the env0 platform is fantastic, one of the many reasons I love working here. The features come thick and fast and this is the motivation behind this monthly blog, to highlight the latest features and showcase Chris’ favorites.
If you want to keep up to date with the features as they are released, follow the changelog.
So far in 2023, we’ve released the following features:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Recommendations for Migrating from Terraform Cloud</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/recommendations-for-migrating-from-terraform-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/recommendations-for-migrating-from-terraform-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is a copy of my env0 post.
In mid-2021, Tim Davis wrote a blog on migrating the state from TFC (Terraform Cloud) to another IaC management platform.
It does a great job of highlighting how TFC and env0 function in terms of both runs and state, or at least it did. Since this original post, the env0 Platform evolution has been quick and with features and improvements coming out every week, it can be hard to keep up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make managing multiple Terraform environments easier</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/how-to-make-managing-multiple-terraform-environments-easier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/env0/how-to-make-managing-multiple-terraform-environments-easier/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is a copy of my env0 post.
How many of you have started with Terraform and discovered you need the same code to build multiple environments? Perhaps a dev, stage, and production environment? After researching Workspaces, Branches, and Terragrunt, you aren’t completely satisfied and want to know if there is another way. If you are here, I’ll assume that’s you!
WorkspacesWorkspaces are a native Terraform construct, offering a reduction in duplicate code and methods of configuring environments differently based on the Workspace name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NSX CSM (Cloud Service Manager)</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/nsx/nsx-csm-cloud-service-manager-ca-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/nsx/nsx-csm-cloud-service-manager-ca-certificate/</guid>
      <description>I recently worked on a customer project where they replaced the NSX Manager certificate with a company-signed certificate using their own CA. This caused an issue when pairing the CSM with the NSX Manager, i.e. certificate error.
This short blog post will run through the steps ran through to allow the CSM to peer with the NSX Manager. I understand this post won’t receive a lot of traffic, my hope is it helps someone in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NSX ALB (Advanced Load Balancer) Design</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/avi-networks-alb/nsx-alb-advanced-load-balancer-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/avi-networks-alb/nsx-alb-advanced-load-balancer-design/</guid>
      <description>I wrote three (3) blogs on Avi Load Balancing, now rebranded as VMware NSX ALB (Advanced Load Balancer). These were around the basic concepts, base configuration, and that configuration using API.
https://www.ulttransformer.com/posts/avi-networks-alb/avi-networks-the-advanced-nsx-load-balancer/ https://www.ulttransformer.com/posts/avi-networks-alb/avi-networks-base-configuration/ https://www.ulttransformer.com/posts/avi-networks-alb/avi-networks-base-configuration-via-api/ I noticed it was difficult to find a single post that discusses the different types of design solutions. In this post, I want to discuss the design decisions when deploying an ALB solution and expand on my previous blogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complement your VDI environment with NSX</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx-advanced-load-balancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx-advanced-load-balancer/</guid>
      <description>Part 1: Complement your VDI environment with NSX Part 2: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: dFW Part 3: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDFW Part 4: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Introspection Services Part 5: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDS/IPS Part 6: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Advanced Load Balancer Thanks to Siegfried Huijgen I ended up receiving a lot of attention on the 5 part series, which spun off into a request for a part 6 on Avi Networks Load Balancing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complement your VDI environment with NSX</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx-ids-ips/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx-ids-ips/</guid>
      <description>Part 1: Complement your VDI environment with NSX Part 2: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: dFW Part 3: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDFW Part 4: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Introspection Services Part 5: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDS/IPS Part 6: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Advanced Load Balancer The final post of this series will be around NSX IDS (Intrusion Detection System) and IPS (Intrusion Prevention System).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complement your VDI environment with NSX</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx-introspection-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx-introspection-services/</guid>
      <description>Part 1: Complement your VDI environment with NSX Part 2: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: dFW Part 3: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDFW Part 4: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Introspection Services Part 5: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDS/IPS Part 6: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Advanced Load Balancer Unfortunately, this post will be more of a theoretical one. I don’t have access to any introspection service providers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complement your VDI environment with NSX</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx-idfw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx-idfw/</guid>
      <description>Part 1: Complement your VDI environment with NSX Part 2: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: dFW Part 3: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDFW Part 4: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Introspection Services Part 5: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDS/IPS Part 6: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Advanced Load Balancer Before I start. Shout out to Bilal Ahmed, a fellow vMusketeer who helped me with this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complement your VDI environment with NSX</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx-dfw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx-dfw/</guid>
      <description>Part 1: Complement your VDI environment with NSX Part 2: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: dFW Part 3: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDFW Part 4: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Introspection Services Part 5: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDS/IPS Part 6: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Advanced Load Balancer I started the series discussing the different features within NSX that can complement a VDI environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complement your VDI environment with NSX</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/complement-your-vdi-environment-with-nsx/</guid>
      <description>Part 1: Complement your VDI environment with NSX Part 2: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: dFW Part 3: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDFW Part 4: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Introspection Services Part 5: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: IDS/IPS Part 6: Complement your VDI environment with NSX: Advanced Load Balancer Over the past few weeks, I’ve been working with a number of customers that are keen to see how NSX can complement their existing or new VDI environment(s).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCDX-NV</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-289/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-289/</guid>
      <description>On Monday 14th of September 2020, I remotely sat the VCDX defence and the following Tuesday, I received the fantastic news that I passed. I am officially VCDX number 289!
For those of you that are new to vMusketeers and my VCDX blogs, here are a link to the previous 3 blogs and a vBrownBag video:
The design document The design defence The scenario defence VCDX motivation (vBrownBag) The experienceI spent a lot of time talking to and working with existing VCDX’s and VCDX applicants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NSX-T Automation using Terraform</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/nsx-t-on-vmc/nsx-t-automation-using-terraform-the-how-vmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/nsx-t-on-vmc/nsx-t-automation-using-terraform-the-how-vmc/</guid>
      <description>I started the series with a post about why I wanted to use Terraform. Now we have the why out of the way, let’s get to the fun stuff… the how!
I use Terraform for 2 things. The first is to spin up SDDC’s on VMC and configure the VMC NSX-T piece. The second is spinning up NSX-T environments in the lab, which will hopefully make it into production one day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NSX-T Automation using Terraform</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/nsx-t-on-vmc/nsx-t-automation-using-terraform-the-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/nsx-t-on-vmc/nsx-t-automation-using-terraform-the-why/</guid>
      <description>Hi all, I hope you are all doing well during these trying times.
For months, possibly even years, I’ve been convincing myself I’d dive into automation. What better time than one where I am forced into isolation with my laptop. In truth, I was jolted into action by a business requirement for automating the build of a number of environments. These environments had to be standardised and utilise many of the same configuration elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avi Networks | NSX ALB</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/avi-networks-alb/avi-networks-base-configuration-via-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/avi-networks-alb/avi-networks-base-configuration-via-api/</guid>
      <description>API ReferenceI wrote a post a few weeks back on how to get an Avi proof of concept up and running. Hopefully, it helped and continues to help others wanting to start playing with Avi.
I like to spin my lab up and down, pushing config when needed. This post will be focused around the Avi APIs and how to stand up the basic configuration previously discussed.
I used the Avi API guide for reference: https://avinetworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avi Networks | NSX ALB</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/avi-networks-alb/avi-networks-base-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/avi-networks-alb/avi-networks-base-configuration/</guid>
      <description>Load BalancingI covered Avi Networks at a high level in my first post. I now want to dive into the base configuration of Avi and at its core, it is a Load Balancer. Saying that there are a few flavours of Load Balancing.
Layer 4 Load Balancing. – Focusing on the IP address and TCP port. Layer 7 Load Balancing. – Focusing on layer 7 attributes such as HTTP headers. Global Server Load Balancing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avi Networks | NSX ALB</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/avi-networks-alb/avi-networks-the-advanced-nsx-load-balancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/avi-networks-alb/avi-networks-the-advanced-nsx-load-balancer/</guid>
      <description>What is Avi?Avi Networks provides software-defined Load Balancing at its core. Complementing the core service is a plethora of mouthwatering services and features. Surely the reason Avi was acquired by VMware on July 11th 2019. Rebranded as the NSX Advanced Load Balancer.
Some of the features include application analytics, predictive autoscaling, micro-segmentation and WAF (Web Application Firewall) all this and on both cloud and on-prem. The Load Balancer for any platform!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCDX-NV</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-defence-scenario/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-defence-scenario/</guid>
      <description>Due to the virus outbreak, my VCDX defence has been postponed until the next window, which is June. The VCDX board decided, understandably, to keep their panellists and applicants as safe as possible. That said, I thought I’d continue the blogging trend and discuss another area of preparation.
Still excited as 3 months will fly by! I’ve discussed the document and design defence. Now let’s look at the defence scenario.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCDX-NV</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-design-defence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-design-defence/</guid>
      <description>I am waiting to hear back on my defence invite, but am preparing like I’ve been invited. Solid advice any VCDX will give you. The design defence is an invitation to Palo Alto, Staines or Sydney to defend your design and run through a scenario. In today’s blog, I am going to talk about my experience when preparing for the design defence.
The design defence is you defending your submitted design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCDX-NV</title>
      <link>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-document-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ulttransformer.com/posts/vcdx/vcdx-nv-document-submission/</guid>
      <description>To start my blogging career, I thought I would talk about my VCDX-NV journey.
I’m currently in the waiting stage after submitting my documents. Waiting for a VCDX panel to determine if my documentation warrants an invite to defend.
Whilst waiting, I thought I’d take this time to share some advice that I found useful on my journey.
Firstly, read and understand the blueprint this can’t be stressed enough. During your journey; you will find all VCDXs repeat this phrase to you, and it’s true.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
